Join Telegram: @lubokvideo - https://telegram.me/lubokvideo
C] ENTERTAINMENT PRESENTS
A BIG STONE PICTURES PRODUCTION
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER
JEONG TAE-SUNG
A KIM HAN-MIN FILM
1597, Second Japanese Invasion
Accused by a Japanese double agent,
Admiral Yi Sun-shin is relieved
of command and tortured.
In July, Joseon's navy is
decimated in Chilcheollyang.
Japan's army advances mercilessly,
capturing two crucial regions in August,
and setting its sights on the capital.
King Seonjo quickly pardons and reinstates Yi,
who immediately rallies his
remaining warships and troops.
He obtains 12 ships that escaped
the battle of Chilcheollyang,
and encamps on the Southern Sea.
Just 20km away in Haenam,
Japan's navy sets up base,
preparing to attack with over 300 ships.
So, Admiral,
when will you join them?
What do you mean?
As per royal order, of course.
Your orders are to join
forces with ground troops
under General Gwon Yul.
Is that what it says?
What?
With all due respect,
the enemy has over 200 ships!
Our men are deserting their posts!
The number of deserters has reached...
50...
I must ease my mind.
200 enemy ships could
invade at any moment!
What strategy...
have you in mind to repel them?
Let's hear from the young officers!
Do we stand a chance?
Do we?
Don't save your breath!
Admiral.
Please help us erase all doubt.
Aside from a damaged turtle ship,
what plan is in place?
You're addressing our commander!
How dare you!
I'm your ranking officer!
Shut your mouth and listen!
You have no right!
You're merely a deserter
who fled from Chilcheollyang!
Boy, we possess those 12 ships,
because I got out from
that doomed battle.
Know when to open your mouth.
Admiral, you know as well as
anyone that this battle is futile.
I saw firsthand the brutality
and strength of our foes!
10,000 men were lost!
Will you knowingly send
the rest of our men to their graves?
This briefing is adjourned.
Dismissed.
Admiral!
He gave an order!
Everyone out.
Our priority is to repair
the ships and train our men!
Now!
We must capture King Seonjo
and end this war.
He mustn't slip through
our fingers like before.
We must coordinate,
like a perfect storm!
Prepare at ONCE!
Yes, commander.
We can't allow Konishi
to dethrone Joseon first.
But Chancellor Hideyoshi
wants us to wait for his man.
So we have no choice.
Aren't those Wakizaka's ships?
Yes, back from reconnaissance.
How many trips?
Three, including last night's.
But sir,
who is the chancellor sending us?
Someone essential
to this battle, I'm told.
One who can overpower Yi Sun-shin.
General
It is futile to battle such a formidable foe. I command
you to disband the navy and join Gwon Yul's army.
Father! Father!
Captain Bae tried,
but they're gonna kill him!
He had to!
We'll die anyway!
Father! Father!
I will...
have your head!
Forgive me for interfering.
I couldn't simply pass by.
Are you the one sent by the chancellor?
It's the navy from Ehime Prefecture.
They're not navy.
Pirates, more like.
Let's move.
Deployment imminent
It's swarming with activity.
Over 200 warships are docked,
supply ships are being loaded,
and they're stealing
provisions from villagers.
They cut off the nose
of any who resist,
and use children for target practice.
It seems as if...
they're on the verge of deployment.
Is it true that
25,000 Japanese reinforcement
soldiers are en route?
Yes, it appears so.
They act like our navy does not exist,
and talk of swarming the capital,
like it was nothing at all.
We must do something,
or the capital will run with blood.
Deliver this to Junsa and
return with his report.
At once, sir.
The figurehead is complete!
Turtle ship's figurehead!
Sweetheart.
Another talisman?
This isn't my first mission.
But I'll treasure it.
I'm off.
Take care of yourself!
Is Yi disobeying
the royal order again?
He pursues what he feels
is a logical path.
If he disobeys the royal order,
I cannot guarantee his safety.
The southern provinces have fallen.
Japan's ground
forces are northbound.
If their navy should also reach
the capital via the southern sea,
what would happen?
But what can he do
with a measly 12 ships?!
How can 12 measly ships
reinforce the army?
Don't mince words!
I know he's not even in good health!
And who's responsible for that?
You son of a...
Do you even know the situation here?
The infamous Kiyomasa is
knocking at our gate.
Ergo! We need every
able body still standing!
Grab him!
LBt go!
Please general,
grant us men and weapons.
The navy is facing a Goliath!
So obey the royal order.
Will you ignore the admiral's
earnest request?
How dare you!
You are out of line!
What are you all waiting for?
Take him away and
lock him up this instant!
General!
Please!
The admiral wishes
to convey these words!
"To forfeit the sea is to forfeit Joseon!"
General! General!
I've waited half a day.
Is this how you treat your guest?
We were too focused on
the war briefing
to give attention to our guest.
I beg your forgiveness.
By the way, how do pirates
usually kill a king?
Please enlighten us.
I've surveyed the region.
If we ride the morning
tide in the strait,
we can resupply the troops by night,
and sail into the capital.
We'll be there in a day and a half.
Easier said than done.
Yi Sun-shin is not a feeble adversary.
Sailing the open sea,
and approaching the capital
to annihilate Yi with
the army is the best strategy.
Why do you think
Hideyoshi sent me, Wakizaka?
How dare you utter his name!
I will crush Yi with this hand.
Will you allow Konishi
to walk into the capital first?
I've committed a grave mistake.
Please forgive my men.
Sit with me, Kurushima.
One swing of this sword, blood will spread
Mother...
Father, it's Hoe.
It's nice to be with you.
Yes, sir.
Father.
Speak freely.
Perhaps this is a blessing in disguise.
Why not blame ailing
health and return home?
We haven't held a proper
funeral for grandmother.
Only a temporary shrine.
Allow our men to join the army,
and say you can no longer
fulfill your duties.
I feel your resentment
towards our king.
The king tried to take your life.
How could you not feel resentment?
Father.
Our fleet is but 12 ships.
It is shameful to call
ourselves a navy.
Even if...
you somehow lead
these men to victory,
the king will surely abandon you.
What are you fighting for?
For loyalty.
To that...
...impudent king?
It is said,
a commander's loyalty
must lie with the king,
and the king must follow his subjects.
Not himself?
The people build a nation.
Only then can a king exist.
Even if...
those people care about nothing
more than their own lives?
Eat your meal, it's precious food.
Make way!
Admiral.
Stay away to avoid beheading
Look... look at this...
That's Captain Bae Hong-suk!
He led the flagship!
Do not enter
Get them out of here!
Get them out!
Get out from there!
Now!
June 7th Kurushima
Michifusa 25 years
Did you behead the prisoners
and send them back?
After cutting off their noses and ears.
Have you a death wish?
Why provoke the enemy
with this senseless act?
Why not? It'll be an interesting fight.
But...
will they fight?
Yi Sun-shin is not a foe to take lightly!
1 hear some of your men
revere 'H's prowess.
Perhaps the defeat in Hansan
has shriveled your balls?
How dare you?
Let me be clear.
Why do you think
the chancellor sent me?
It's because of men like you
who tremble at Yi's name.
Don't draw your sword so recklessly.
Your head may be the first to fall.
My brother Michiyuki became
minion to the chancellor,
and died on his quest
to conquer Joseon.
With me facing the chancellor's wrath,
he joined this war to save me,
and died by 'H's hand.
The chancellor is ill,
he has a year at most.
That's why he's rushing this campaign.
Joseon, which he so desires,
will fall to me.
That is why Yi must perish.
Do you understand, Haru?
Perhaps this will also be
proper revenge for my brother.
Why did he do it?
Isn't that Oh Sang-go?
He got caught trying to flee!
It is! It's Sang-go!
He was captured near
Blood Isle while fleeing.
My comrades of 6 years
all died in Chilcheollyang.
Today I buried them
with my own hands...
I couldn't help myself.
Now, my turn will come.
Must all of us...
die in vain?
Are you finished?
Discipline stands!
In any situation!
Is that clear?
There's no way out now.
He'll kill even his own.
There is...
always a way.
As the bottleneck of the strait,
the current is very strong here.
They say it is so treacherous,
nothing can escape.
Is it here, sir?
Sir, we can assume that
they'll only enter this strait
if they see it as an advantage.
Look at those waves.
They'll ride those waves
and ram into our ships.
We don't stand a chance.
That's why we need the turtle ship.
Use it to break the front line,
and our warships can fire
cannons from a distance.
It takes half a day
for the tide to change,
will the turtle ship hold?
When the tide changes,
the sea calms considerably.
But that sound...
has changed from what is was before.
It is like the sound of
a man's howling.
The real problem is the whirlpool.
You rarely hear the sound
during high tide.
But if somehow
you should hear it then,
a giant whirlpool appears.
High tide comes in 2 days,
and so it could only mean...
Do you hear it?
I hear that sound...
as the howling of men
lost in Chilcheollyang.
Is the turtle ship your only tactic?
Tactics are not the problem.
It's the fear that is spreading
among my men like a virus.
Is there a way to overcome it?
What are we to do if we cannot?
Is beheading our own men,
like this morning,
the only means of discipline?
Can we achieve victory that way?
But you...
We can use it.
YOU mean...
the fear?
Admiral...
It is unjust...
Avenge us...
So good to see you.
Welcome, Hong-suk.
Captain Choi, Captain Lee...
Avenge us...
Come...
accept my drink.
Please take this drink.
Men...
Where are you going?
Captain Lee...
Hong-suk...
Please!
Why must you rush off?
Father!
The turtle ship's on fire!
Admiral!
It's General Bae Seol's first mate.
Put out the fire!
Hurry!
Put it out!
Bring water!
Over there!
Hear me!
Don't you want to live?!
A dying man...
is leading us to the gates of Hell!
But, I...
...have found a way out!
Do not senselessly
throw away your lives!
So join me!
NO...
Can't be...
Admiral, it's too dangerous!
Please no!
No!
It can't be!
- Admiral!
- Let me go!
No!
Our turtle ship!
Father, it's all over!
There's nothing we can do!
Only one day from completion!
I will face them with this turtle ship!
No!
Commander Todo! Commander Todo!
Yi's turtle ship has burned.
What?
A scout was sent after spotting
fire and smoke from Yi's base,
and the ship is now ashes!
It was his last turtle
ship, was it not?
YES.
Yi does not have any turtle ships left.
Taito mumun...
"Do not look back when
the only course is forward."
I feel your great resolve
in the calligraphy.
This is the spirit
we need at this junction.
Prepare for battle!
Junsa... where are you...
What happened here?
Help!
Grab him!
Get him!
Please! Help me!
Help me!
Hurry LIP!
Find the other one!
Find him!
Hurry LIP!
March!
I'm from a fishing village,
and I can row very well!
Really good rower! One of the best!
What's he jabbering?
What the hell?
Ski-bong!
You little rat!
Wait! I'm sorry!
Please don't kill me!
Calm down!
Whirlpool...
Turtle ship...
Father!
A message from Junsa!
We'll reach Myeongnyang
tomorrow morning.
We deploy with the tide,
and the fleet is over 330 ships.
Captain of the vanguard is,
unfortunately, someone new.
His name is Kurushima,
known as the Pirate King,
and versed in similar conditions.
Fortunately, backing him up
is General Wakizaka,
whom you defeated in Hansan.
I hope you find some comfort in this.
I will join you once I fulfill my duty.
Let's go to Usuyeong.
- Sir?
- We cannot fight with the strait behind us.
We must move our men now!
To war!
Run as fast as the wind,
stand still as the trees
A message from General Konishi.
He's pressing me.
We will reach the king before him.
We're ready for deployment.
Joseon looks particularly savory today.
I like this land.
Captain.
Status.
All prepared, sir.
There are only POWs below deck,
and we've stockpiled the gunpowder.
Yi Sun-shin...
will not survive this.
To war!
Not even a turtle ship!
Does a single line formation
even qualify as a tactic?!
Has the admiral gone mad?
He's right!
Just listen to that!
We can't all die in vain.
We must come up with a new plan!
A new plan!
And what could that be?
Could you be implying that
we assassinate the admiral?
No!
That's not what I'm saying!
Time is of the essence,
and we can't even send
a message up the ranks.
Let's go to him.
To who?
I'll convince the admiral, if not...
I'll offer up my life instead.
Your Majesty,
if you disband the navy now,
I'm afraid the enemy will
reach you unimpeded.
I still have 12 ships at my command.
If we fight to our last breath,
it is not impossible.
As long as I still breathe...
the enemy shall never
feel safe on our soil.
Admiral.
At the risk of my own life,
I'd like to speak my mind.
Sir!
This battle is futile!
It's futile!
Even if we lure the enemy
into the narrow strait,
we cannot face them
without a single turtle ship!
Save this battle
for another day! Please!
Please!
Is that how you really feel?
Please take my life,
if you believe otherwise.
I'd rather die by your sword!
If that is how you feel, very well.
Gather all the men
in front of the camp.
Yes, sir!
General
Captains Kim and Hwang,
have you brought it?
Yes, admiral!
Pour it!
What are you waiting for?
- Pour it!
- Yes, sir!
Light it!
Sir!
Admiral Yi!
Stand back!
It's shameful that you still
only consider your own lives!
Death...
is unavoidable!
Is avoiding combat
the path to survival?
Will we be safe on land?
Behold!
I am burning this land
so that I can die at sea.
This is where we stand and fight!
Do not hold onto life!
If you crave life, you will surely die!
If you fight to the death, you will live!
One man at the strategic point
can fend off a thousand men!
Those words were spoken
to describe our situation now!
Father.
How will you utilize
this cancerous fear?
Is this Captain Bae Hong-suk's son?
Yes, sir.
He brought Junsa's message
instead of our scout.
Junsa encountered him
by chance and helped him escape.
This was your father's.
Will you accept it?
What is your name?
Bae Su-bong, sir.
With your father by my side,
we fought for 6 years.
I will not forget your
father and your names.
I...
I have a request, sir.
Go on.
Please allow me to board
your ship and fight for you!
Only if you'll take an oar
rather than a sword.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Mother.
I must be off now.
My only wish is that
our death will not be in vain.
Admiral.
Good work.
We offer you our assistance.
It is greatly appreciated.
Admiral!
Junsa, thank you.
Full deployment.
Full deployment!
Let's go to war!
Deploy!
Battle formation.
The current's pushing us back!
Row harder!
Drum louder!
Load the cannons!
We must hold our position!
Row harder!
Get rid of it.
- Look!
- What is that?
What's that black mass?
Our fleet!
Close the lid!
Su-bong, I think
we boarded the wrong ship.
Didn't know it was the flagship?
But why must the flagship
be at the front?!
I'll order our fleet to
remain in formation!
Let them be.
Sir? But admiral...
Lower the anchor
and prepare for battle.
Lower the anchor!
Why isn't Yi raising his command flag?
Just look at them.
Even if he did, would
his men follow him?
Vanguard 1, advance.
Vanguard 1!
Advance!
Rotate starboard
and prepare the cannons.
Prepare the cannons!
Starboard oars, stop!
Port oars, row faster!
Lieutenant Nah!
Captain Song!
Aim all cannons and explosive
arrows at their vanguard ships!
Yes, sir!
Aim the cannons at the vanguard!
Archers, battle station!
Aim!
Prepare to fire!
Ready!
Fire!
The current is picking up,
steer carefully!
Ready to fire!
- Fire!
Now!
Increase speed and rotate to port!
Fire!
Watch out!
Yi is concentrating attack
on the front line.
Vanguard ships are
colliding into one another.
Yi's holding his position.
Could he be waiting for something?
Shouldn't we join the assault
and reinforce the front?
NO...
Wait a little longer.
Fear does not discriminate,
it can equally affect our enemy.
Six years of defeat have
planted fear in their men, too.
Fear does not discriminate...
Is that all?
Is that how we use fear?
If only we can turn fear into courage.
Send in vanguard 2, and press harder.
Vanguard 2!
Advance!
Kurushima keeps sending in ships.
He's very skilled
in handling strong tides.
Let's wait and see.
Just watch.
The current is on our side.
We will demolish them.
Admiral! Due to the current,
our accuracy has gone down!
Cut the anchor lose.
Ride the current towards Blood Isle.
Right away!
They're trapped.
Fire!
Get the poles!
Port oars, row harder!
We mustn't hit the rocks!
Sir! We must alert our fleet!
We won't last long
at our current position!
Switch to shrapnel shells.
And prepare for close combat.
Get ready!
For close combat!
Now!
Fire!
Board!
Kurushima is about to win the battle!
Yi held his ground long enough.
We're all going to die!
Admiral!
Gather all cannons
to the port oar of the ship.
Can you do it?
But we could all die!
Just get it done!
Yes, sir! It will be done!
Hold your ground!
Place cannons on port oar opening!
What are you waiting for?!
Get the shells!
- It's too dangerous, don't do it!
- Hurry up!
Gather the shells and gunpowder!
On the double!
One swing of this sword,
blood will spread
Admiral!
We're ready!
Brace yourselves!
Hit the deck!
Is that how we use fear?
If only we can turn fear into courage...
It will inspire even more courage.
But father...
How can we possibly inspire
such courage in our men?
I must be sacrificed.
Could this be...
the end?
Look!
The flagship survived!
It's still standing!
Destroy the enemy!
Sons of bitches!
I'll kill them all!
I want to kill, too!
Full speed ahead!
Whirlpool...
It's the whirlpool...
Yi Sun-shin...
So there was a reason
why you were holding out there.
The current has changed,
a large whirlpool is forming!
Thanks to that, the water
near the isle is calm,
which greatly increases their accuracy.
If he holes up there,
no one can pass the strait.
And the battle will be over.
Maximum speed to the flagship,
before he gets in formation!
Sir, that's their main fleet.
Raise the flag.
Yes, sir.
You're mine.
Admiral!
Captain Ahn!
You must be disciplined
under strict martial law,
but as we're at war,
I command you to fight to the death!
Defend Blood Isle with your life!
Understood?!
Yes, admiral!
We must reach the center
of the strait quickly.
Yes, admiral!
To the center of the strait!
Impeccable timing, sir.
The explosion will be massive.
We won't fa“ for 'H's decoy.
Our main fleet will
continue towards the isle.
Sir!
A straw-covered ship is approaching!
Archers in formation!
Yes, sir!
Fire!
We're sitting ducks!
Haul out the water!
Hurry!
We're out of shells on the deck!
It severed my chain!
Grab his sword!
Lim Jun-young?
Junsa!
It's carrying gunpowder?
Admiral, that vessel is
carrying gunpowder.
Our scout Lim is on board.
No response from Ahn's ship?!
Load the cannons immediately!
Admiral, there's no answer!
Wave something and
make them fire at me!
This ship...
mustn't reach the admiral!
YOU must!
Good...
That's it...
Let's all signal!
Everyone, hurry!
Captain!
Over there!
A straw ship heading for the flagship!
Get ready to fire!
Yes, sir!
Ready!
Fire!
Good work.
So happy to see you,
one last time...
Admiral!
Their vanguard flagship
is heading for us!
The enemy's coming!
Grab your oars!
Finish him off!
Close combat!
Board their ship!
Kuroda!
Hurry!
Should we reinforce?
We're shorthanded!
Let's reinforce our men on the deck!
Ski-bong!
Yi Sun-shin! You're mine!
Admiral! Our ships have
come to our aid!
Kimura!
Catch up to them!
We've lost control...
Load!
Fire!
You must request reinforcements!
There is none.
We're on our own.
Shouldn't we reinforce them?
Yi Sun-shin.
Are you...
a SPY or a traitor?!
Yi Sun-shin!
Sir.
I'm afraid our ship is failing...
Admiral!
We'll pull you out!
Our fleet is coming!
We must destroy them
before they get into formation!
Why aren't we going faster?!
But the tide has turned...
I know that!
Whip the rowers to row faster!
Speed! I need speed!
That's our only chance!
Full speed!
Don't let go of the oars!
Hang in there!
When will this end, damn it?!
We're free!
Admiral!
Here is my order!
General
It can't be...
Brace for impact!
They're coming in hard!
No!
Please, hold on a bit longer.
They broke the front line.
Risen from the dead!
Rebirth of the turtle ship!
It has returned!
Was that...
a part of his plan all along?
They're fleeing! Look at them!
Fire!
Do not look back when the only course is forward
Yi Sun-shin...
Retreat!
Turn the ship around.
The tide has again turned in our favor.
Battle report!
31 ships destroyed!
No ally ships lost!
Invade all they want, they can't
do nothing on our watch!
- Have some.
- I'm already full!
I looked one in the eye
and he pissed his pants!
I'm the best!
Will history remember
how hard we fought?
Every damn minute.
You speak the truth!
We're still breathing,
it's time to go back home.
You said it!
Here, have a drink!
Isn't this taro?
It feels good to eat.
Admiral!
HOW can we ease...
their suffering...
Father.
How did you think of
using the whirlpool?
Father?
What did you ask me?
The whirlpool appeared at our
most desperate moment.
If it weren't for that...
It was the grace of God.
The grace of God?
You mean we could've
been defeated?
Yes, indeed.
If the peasants didn't save me then...
Peasants were the grace of God?
Not the whirlpool?
Which do you think it is?
There...
What is that?
CHOI MIN-SIK
RYU SEUNG-RYONG
CHO JIN-WOONG
KIM MYEONG-GON JIN GOO LEE JEONG-HYUN
WRITTEN BY
JEON CHUL-HONG KIM HAN-MIN
DIRECTED BY
KIM HAN-MIN