Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hello, Adri.
Um, this isn't easy.
I wasn't strong enough
to tell you face-to-face.
Maybe this is the way
to avoid useless arguments.
I'm leaving.
I love you so much...
...but I can't carry on with you.
Please don't look for me,
and don't hate me.
THE HIDDEN FACE
Good evening.
What are you having?
Whiskey with one ice cube, please.
Right away.
I don't like seeing men cry.
When a man cries,
it's because he feels guilty.
Not always.
Excuse me. We're closing up.
Never mind.
Are you all right?
No, I'm not all right.
What's up, pal?
What are you doing?
Leave him, he's drunk. Let's go.
But he hit me! Didn't you see?
- Let's go. It's over.
- Sure, sure.
What happened?
Why did they hit you?
Nothing happened.
Careful.
Ooh. Ah.
Does it hurt?
No, it's nothing.
You can't go like this.
I'll call a taxi. Where do you live?
Where do I live?
- No.
- What are you doing? Ha, ha.
I'm conducting.
What's the tempo?
Don't turn it down, I'm conducting.
Forcefully.
Don't fall down.
One, two, almost there.
Three, four. Good.
- Careful.
- Where's a sofa?
Careful.
Good morning.
Where am I?
My Place.
I have to go.
Adrian, isn't it? I'm Fabiana.
- How do you know my name?
- You told me.
What happened last night?
Why were you fighting?
I really have to go.
Thank you.
That's all for today.
Whiskey with one ice cube.
I came to apologize.
I was a dick this morning.
Yes, that's true.
I also wanted to thank you
for helping me.
You didn't have to.
- Anyone would've done it.
- No, I don't think so.
Excuse me.
Would you like to sit with me?
No, I can't, I have to work.
Sure. Then I suggest something.
What?
Wow, this is incredible.
The instruments are arranged
from lesser to greater volume.
First the strings:
violins, violas, cellos and basses.
Then woodwinds,
horns and percussion at the back.
And that's it.
It's a very special place.
Thanks for bringing me.
You're welcome.
- I like seeing you like this.
- Like what?
Relaxed, happy, okay.
I bet you're married
or have a girlfriend.
Neither.
I like this mirror.
Fabiana.
Hello.
- Have you been up long?
- No.
Want some breakfast?
Let's go.
This place is huge.
Why don't you live in the city?
It's quieter. I concentrate better.
Nature is inspiring.
Yes, but not just the beautiful side.
I like what's behind too,
hidden, you know?
Hmm.
- When do you go to work?
- I'm not working today.
No? I am.
Sleep here tonight.
I'll pick you up later.
All right.
Okay.
Morning, maestro.
- Morning.
Maestro.
I assume there's no news
of Miss Belen Echeverria.
- I don't know anything.
- Have you got company?
Are we interrupting?
Come in.
BUITRAGO If I may.
Nice to meet you, miss.
Francisco Jose Buitrago, DA's office.
Fabiana Caicedo.
- Bernardo Ramirez, my partner.
- How are you?
Your girlfriend hasn't left the country.
I confirmed it with Immigration.
- We want to look at the house.
- Is that necessary?
Absolutely, maestro. You never know.
- What was your name?
- Fabiana Caicedo.
Fabiana. If I may.
Ah.
Beautiful.
Very nice. Very nice.
Congratulations, a very pretty house.
- Thanks a lot.
- Yours, isn't it?
Rented.
How long have you lived here?
Almost two months.
Did Miss Echeverria leave anything?
A few things in the bathroom.
Creams, a toothbrush.
And work items. That's her workshop.
What's going on?
She didn't disappear.
She left me for another man.
- The police are investigating.
- It's routine.
They don't know anything.
Her friends or family in Spain?
I tried every means to contact her.
They never replied.
Nor do I want to alarm anyone.
Aren't you worried?
Of course, but I know she's all right.
You don't think she's dead?
No.
- What if she was kidnapped?
- Please.
Do they think I've got her buried
in the garden?
What are you doing?
Come up, it's late.
- I'll be right there.
- I'll be waiting.
- Fabiana.
- Adrian, don't scare me.
What's wrong?
I don't like the lights going out
in this place.
They do when it rains. It's fine.
Are you all right?
Come here.
See? It comes back on its own.
Ha, ha. Don't be scared.
You're so clean.
You left me waiting.
The water was lovely.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yes.
Can you get the dog out, please?
Hans, out.
Fabiana, don't you think
it's a bit rushed...
...this guy going out with you
just after his girl vanished?
No, I don't.
I wouldn't be so calm if I were you.
- Why?
- He's a suspect.
That doesn't mean he is guilty.
Besides, she left him.
We don't know that for sure.
Are you jealous?
You finally got what you wanted,
a guy with money.
Better than a cop with a shit salary.
You may be right.
Tito.
The orchestra manager. Remember?
I'd like you to meet Fabiana.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Oh, I saw you.
I was right behind you in the concert.
Roberto Peña.
Fabiana Caicedo. Nice to meet you.
Tito makes sure all this
comes off perfectly.
He's a wonderful boss.
On the contrary, Adrian,
you know we were lucky...
...and privileged to have you.
The orchestra and I won't forget you.
I'll miss you when I go, which is soon.
That's life.
Hans.
Out. Get out of here.
Who's there?
Adrian?
Who is it?
Does it still hurt? Here.
In half an hour it won't hurt any more.
All right?
I don't want to be alone in this house.
What if something bad happened to me?
Nothing happened.
The lights went because of the rain,
and the dog scared you, that's all.
No? What happened?
I think there's a ghost.
- Ha, ha. Fabiana...
- Don't laugh, I'm serious.
What ghost? Where is it?
It's here. Listen.
Right...
- Hear it?
- There is a weird sound.
See?
It could be the wind
through the plumbing.
No?
Hmm.
Ghost down there...
...if you bother Fabiana,
you'll be dealing with me, all right?
I think that'll do it.
No, something's going on here.
Don't worry.
Let's go to sleep.
I'll put ice on your head.
Thanks.
Yes.
Yes, that's me.
What?
Yes, I'll be there in half an hour.
What's wrong?
What happened?
It was the DA's office.
They say they've found a body
that could be Belen.
They want me to identify the body.
We have the body here of a young lady
with similar characteristics...
...to Miss Belen Echeverria,
and we want you to help us identify her.
- Very well.
- Follow me.
Mr. Salamanca.
- Hello.
Her face is unrecognizable
due to the fire.
It was impossible to identify her.
It's not Belen.
- Are you sure, maestro?
- Completely.
FABIANA I'm sorry.
- Hi.
- Who were you talking to?
- What happened out there?
- To nobody. I was looking for a book.
How did it go?
- Was it her?
- No.
Belen is no longer in my life.
All right?
I love you.
Are you following me or not?
Why this great honor, you cooking?
- I cook a lot.
- Yeah.
I have to tell you something.
Good or bad?
Well...
Remember I was a candidate
to conduct the Bogota Philharmonic?
- Yes.
- They called me today...
...and they've chosen me.
Really?
- Adri, really?
- Ha, ha. Yes.
Congratulations, honey.
That's great.
I'm so happy, I really am.
I leave in 15 days.
In 15 days?
- For how long?
- A year.
A year?
Well, then...
- I don't know.
- You are coming with me?
What, to Bogotá?
You want me to go to Bogotá
for a year with you in 15 days?
What do I do about my job,
for example?
Come and then we'll see.
Okay.
If I come with you,
do you promise to take care of me?
- Is that a yes?
- Yes.
What?
You won't leave me alone?
You'll be with me?
Mm, I won't leave you alone
for one second.
Adrian was wonderful.
There are very few conductors
of his age with such talent.
I wasn't wrong to get him.
No, you have a good eye.
- So do you.
- Well, I'll get him.
- Well done, Tito.
- Congratulations to you too.
Thanks.
Yes.
- Hi.
- Hi, Belen.
How are you? I was looking for you.
I was saying goodbye to Veronica.
Remember her?
- Sure. How are you?
- How are you?
Great.
- Did you like the concert?
- Very much. You were all great.
Let's go.
- Yes.
- Bye.
I didn't know
you were such a good conductor, sir.
Excuse me, miss,
are you trying to pick me up?
I won't deny it. I am a little.
- And are you picking me up?
- Who else?
- I don't know.
- "I don't know"?
- Eh?
- I'm just kidding, silly. Ha, ha.
I know you only have eyes for me.
This house was built
by a very interesting Italian architect...
...a very famous one.
- Oh, please.
- Ha, ha. This is my dog, Hans.
He's a good dog, aren't you, Hans?
Hello, Hans. You're gorgeous.
It seems he likes you.
I love dogs.
Then some modifications were done.
I took care of the garden.
Botany is my passion.
- Is your husband German too?
- He was.
He came to Colombia to work,
and I followed him, in love.
A toast to that.
Mm. You have a piano.
It's not just any piano,
it's a very fine German piano.
- May I?
- Sure.
- Do you play?
- No, not a note.
But my boyfriend does.
He conducts the philharmonic.
Oh, yes? How marvelous.
- Like you, I followed him to Colombia.
- Ah.
That's love.
For some time, I've been living
in a small flat in the city.
I only spend weekends here.
Here we have the bathroom.
I'm going back to Berlin in a month.
I've got mixed feelings about it.
If you like the house,
you can have it when you like.
- There's only one drawback.
- What's that?
The person who stays
has to look after my dog, Hans.
No, no problem. As I said, I love dogs.
Fabulous.
Adrian.
What's the purpose of the table here?
- I don't quite understand.
- It's a great position.
Hans, get off.
So looking at the leather first...
...I like this one best,
for the texture and color.
It'd mean making one
with a rubber wedge like this...
...and another with a wooden heel.
Excuse me a second.
Hi, Emma. Good.
Yes, he's with me,
and he's behaving really well.
Oh, perfect.
Hans will be so happy to see you.
Okay, see you tomorrow, then.
- Who's this beastie?
- That's Hans.
Is it a problem letting him loose here?
No, we love dogs here,
and dogs love music.
Hello, Belen.
Sorry, am I interrupting?
Are you still rehearsing?
- No, I was talking to Veronica.
- Hello, Belen.
All right, then.
Finish your whiskey, rehearse...
I'll see you in the car.
I'll go too.
Miss Veronica, you appear to have
forgotten your violin.
Maestro.
- We weren't doing anything.
- And I'm not saying anything.
Aren't you going to talk
for the whole trip?
Belen?
Do you take all your musicians into
your office, or just the girl violinists?
Can't I speak to the musicians?
Sure, but talking and flirting
aren't the same thing.
- You're exaggerating.
- I'm exaggerating?
Yes.
I've seen you with her before.
- When?
- Forget it.
Do what you like.
It's your problem if you screw up.
Don't get a shock if one day you wake up
and I'm not there.
I'm sorry.
- How are the new designs?
- Fine.
Have you sent the sketches to Spain?
Yes, last week. They're very pleased.
Is the leather here all right?
- Fine, good quality.
- That's great.
I'm going.
Adrian?
What is it?
What have you got going
with that violinist Veronica?
Jeez, Belen.
I've got nothing going on with her.
Then why do you call
and text each other?
You looked at my phone?
Answer me.
I flirted with her a little, that's all.
Nothing happened.
I couldn't do anything to hurt you.
Then why flirt with her?
- We all flirt.
- No...
...we don't all flirt.
I love you and I'm with you.
There is nothing else.
What can I do for you to believe me?
Fire Veronica?
All right, fire her.
- I can't do that.
- Okay.
Get going. You'll be late.
It's fine.
I just need to be alone, that's all.
I left behind my life in Spain
to come here with him...
...and I don't know
if it was the right decision.
My husband was very involved
with his work.
It always came first.
But he couldn't live without me.
What did your husband do?
He was an engineer.
He had a prodigious mind.
He wooed me with it.
Can you believe it?
Sometimes I wonder...
...what would happen
if something happened to me...
...if I died or something.
How would Adrian react?
Why don't you test him?
What do you mean, "test"?
Yes, teach him a little lesson.
Love has to be absolute, doesn't it?
Can you keep a secret?
Come with me.
My husband felt
they could come for him...
...at any time,
like others in South America.
So he built this place.
He was obsessed with it.
He said it was a place
where one could die in peace.
And so he did.
Go in.
Reinforced glass, one-way vision.
Utterly soundproof.
It's hermetically sealed.
This is a dynamo to turn on the light.
Look.
See?
With this speaker,
you can hear everything outside.
This is crazy.
And here?
It's strange.
I haven't come in here for a long time.
Thank you
for showing me your secret.
It's ours now.
- Goodbye.
- All the best. Take care.
- I'll call you when I get to Berlin.
- Okay.
- All the best.
- Thanks.
Have a nice trip.
And thanks for everything, Emma.
You're welcome. Take care, eh?
Hello, Adrian. I'm leaving
because I've met someone...
...at the gym, and he gets me hot.
Hello, Adrian.
Look, I'm off to Spain,
and you know why?
Because I'm fucking fed up.
Hello, Adri.
Um, this isn't easy.
I wasn't strong enough
to tell you face-to-face.
Maybe this is the way
to avoid useless arguments.
I'm leaving.
I love you so much...
...but I can't carry on with you.
I think this is the best for both of us.
Please don't look for me,
and don't hate me.
VIDEO
FOR ADRIAN
Hello, Adri.
Um, this isn't easy.
I wasn't strong enough
to tell you face-to-face.
Belen, I just saw the video.
I don't get it.
I don't know what's going on.
Call me when you can, okay?
Adrian! Adri, I'm here! I'm here! Adri!
Adrian! Adrian!
No, don't go, Adri!
Holy shit.
Come on.
Fuck!
Adrian! Adrian!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Adri.
I'm so sorry.
I love you.
Adri.
Help me.
...but I can't carry on with you.
I think this is the best for both of us.
Please don't look for me,
and don't hate me.
- Do you suspect anyone?
- What do you mean, "suspect anyone"?
She's a beautiful woman.
Suddenly there's an admirer,
a friend, a lover.
No. We hardly know anyone here.
She was alone a lot, but I doubt it.
This was the 8th of August,
the last day you saw her.
- Yes.
Mm-hm.
Mr. Peña?
I saw her the day before.
She came here.
Did she say anything
that could help us?
Why don't you tell them, Adrian?
- We argued. Nothing important.
- Everything's important here.
A couple's spat, that's all.
What happened was that
Belen surprised Adrian...
...with a member of the orchestra.
Nothing happened,
they were having a drink...
...but Belen was annoyed.
It's not important, it isn't. What's
important is finding out where she is.
- That's what we have to find out.
- We have to wait now.
Maybe she'll turn up.
Maestro, we have no traces
of a kidnapping or forced disappearance.
We'll go to Immigration
and see if she left the country.
We'll check your house
to see if something can help us find her.
So you don't think anything bad
happened to her?
These cases
are more common than you might think.
Even in this country.
- All the best.
- What?
Adri.
What do you mean, "all the best"?
What does "all the best" mean?
Adrian.
You can't say that!
It couldn't be worse!
Adrian!
Adrian, look at the ripples!
Adri, look at them!
Adri, no. Adrian!
Adri!
Fucking hell.
What's wrong with this?
Come on.
Don't do this to me, please.
I like this mirror.
No, please, no.
Adri, please don't do this.
Stop it, please, stop.
Stop!
Stop it! Shut up!
Where the hell did you come from?
That's my toothbrush.
Fucking bitch.
Help!
Help! Here! Help!
Oh, I scalded you.
What a bummer, eh?
Sorry, but I've got to do it.
You understand, don't you, Fabiana?
Fabiana!
Fabiana, can you hear me?
Hans.
Out. Get out of here.
Fuck.
Having a great time, huh?
How old are you? Five?
What are you doing?
The key. Fabiana.
You've found the key, Fabiana.
Okay, now think. Fabiana, listen to me.
Very good, Fabiana. Listen to me.
Listen to me. Think.
What are you doing?
Don't do that! It's not a necklace!
Listen to me!
Why do the lights cut out
in this shitty house?
Fabiana, no. The key, Fabiana!
Will you pass me that?
Thanks.
Yes. Yes, that's me.
What?
What's wrong?
They say they've found a body
that could be Belen.
Don't smile, bitch, I'm not dead.
Well, you're not as thick as I thought.
Start.
Stop.
Good, Fabiana. No.
Don't stop now. Fabiana, come back.
That's it, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Start.
Stop.
Is anyone there?
Yes!
Are you talking to me?
- Good, Fabiana.
- Adrian, is it you?
Don't play with me.
Come on. Come on.
- Papa?
- No.
Christ, Fabiana, think.
- Belen?
- Yes!
Come on, Fabiana.
- Are you dead?
- You wish. Come on.
Are you alive?
Are you trapped?
Yes!
Did Adrian lock you up?
No. Come on, Fabiana, keep asking.
Keep going.
Behind the mirror?
Yes!
Good, Fabiana, good.
No.
The other mirror is the door?
Yes!
Good, Fabiana.
Come on.
The ward robe, Fabiana.
The wardrobe.
How the hell do I tell you?
The wardrobe, the wardrobe.
Very good, Fabiana.
Yes.
Fabiana, what are you doing?
Fabiana!
Why won't you open up?
What the fuck are you doing?
Open up!
I'm sorry.
- Hi.
- Who were you talking to?
- What happened out there?
- To nobody. I was looking for a book.
How did it go? Was it her?
- Fucking bitch.
- No.
Fucking bitch.
Fabiana, you fucking bitch! Open up!
Fabiana, you fucking bitch...
...you can't leave me here.
Fabiana, open up!
You can't leave me here!
Open up! Open up!
Adrian.
What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep.
Are you all right?
Go to bed. I'll be right there.
Relax, Hans.
Relax, it's all right.
It's all right, relax.
Maestro Salamanca.
- Ramirez.
- Everything all right?
Fine.
It's my duty to inform you
that as a judicial officer...
...Miss Belen Echeverria
is now my case.
Officer Buitrago called me this morning
to tell me.
I hope you find her soon.
- We'll do all we can.
- Thanks a lot.
Do you want something?
Listen, maestro,
be very careful what you do.
What's wrong with you?
I don't really care much
about your girlfriend.
But if something happens to Fabiana,
I'll kill you.
- Everything all right?
- Yes, thanks.
- Hi.
- Can I have one?
- You don't smoke.
What about the Spaniard?
- What about him?
- How's it going with him?
Fine.
So are you going to Spain with him?
- We'll see what happens.
- And the girlfriend?
I don't know.
It's better she doesn't turn up, eh?
Belen.
Belen, are you all right?
ARE YOU
OKAY?
What happened?
Hello.
Why did you change
everything around?
I wanted to surprise you.
This bathroom works properly.
- Oh, yes?
- Yes.
And the view from here is nicer.
Do you mind?
No, but I wish you'd asked me first.
I thought you'd like it.
It's fine.
- Adrian's not here.
- No? And where is he?
Working.
That's what you think.
Take care of yourself, Fabiana.
Veronica.
Hello.
Let's see.
I like you a lot.
I love hanging out with you,
but what we're doing...
I can't go on.
Okay.
People, we'll begin on C.
Wind instruments, you are the melody.
Stand out, all right?
Violas, basses and cellos,
heavy on the triplets.
Yes?
Let's go.
One and two and...
Belen.
Belen. Belen.
This message
is for Miss Belen Echeverria.
I inform you that Emma Engel
has passed away in Berlin.
The family wants to sell the house
from Germany, so I need you to...
Translated by:
Silvia Grumaches Cortina, Raul E. Reyes
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org